<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post/2008/augusts on Journal</title>
    <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2008/august/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post/2008/augusts on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 15:22:18 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://life.jessicah.org/post/2008/august/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear of Flying</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2008/august/fear-of-flying/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 15:22:18 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2008/august/fear-of-flying/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve never travelled internationally before. Initially, I had been getting increasingly excited about visiting Portland and Victoria. Now, however, I&amp;rsquo;m getting scared. Intensely scared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only fix days to go until I depart for the States, and the realisation of just how unprepared I am is setting in. And the stress and worry and other fears is overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m scared of not meeting peoples expectations. I&amp;rsquo;m scared of something going horribly wrong with my flights, and being stuck in a foregin country without a clue. I&amp;rsquo;m terrified of the thought of possibly facing harsher prejudice than I do here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try as I might to quell my fears, they only seem to grow stronger. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how I&amp;rsquo;m going to do this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am genuinely scared&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuck</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2008/august/stuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 19:26:46 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2008/august/stuck/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You may or may not know this about me, but I&amp;rsquo;m a Christian. Presently, however, I&amp;rsquo;ve found myself in a love-hate relationship with God that I&amp;rsquo;m unable to break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A while ago, I was struggling with other issues, when suddenly Psalm 139 started popping up everywhere, and one person had prayed it over me. That&amp;rsquo;s when everything started to go more down hill&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s this one verse that is the cause of my relationship trouble with God. Psalm 139:13 reads &amp;ldquo;For You created my inmost being; You knit me together in my mother&amp;rsquo;s womb.&amp;rdquo; (NIV)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;rsquo;t go into more personal details of my life, but basically I wasn&amp;rsquo;t put together the way I should&amp;rsquo;ve been, and for a verse like that to say that God did this to me hurts. It truly, deeply hurts. And now I hate God for how He put me together with a passion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, I still go to church; I still worship Him and sing His praises. Perhaps I don&amp;rsquo;t mean it as much as I had been, but it&amp;rsquo;s not a complete separation from God. Admittedly, I haven&amp;rsquo;t read my Bible since, but I still talk to God and try to pray for other issues in my life, and other people and their situations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have noticed a lot of things going wrong lately though. A coincidence? Or is this the flak I get for hating God?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>