<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post/2010/augusts on Journal</title>
    <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/august/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post/2010/augusts on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 19:27:41 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/august/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Push Ups Program</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/august/push-ups-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 19:27:41 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/august/push-ups-program/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I randomly arrived at &lt;a href=&#34;http://hundredpushups.com/&#34;&gt;one hundred pushups&lt;/a&gt; a couple days ago from a link in comments to a post on &lt;a href=&#34;http://lifehacker.com/&#34;&gt;Life Hacker&lt;/a&gt;. After reading through the website, I decided to follow their well-thought out program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Completing day one of week one, the program feels entirely achievable. Doing pushups until failure is extremely tough, leaving my body trembling after the intense exertion. I&amp;rsquo;m constantly surprised how such seemingly simple exercises easily push the body to the limit, reminding me of Pilates-type exercises&amp;mdash;despite doing only stretches, I&amp;rsquo;m left pouring in sweat, thoroughly exhausted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The program lasts about six weeks, and I highly encourage all of you who read my journal to challenge yourself to complete the program too!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falls to Climb</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/august/falls-to-climb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2010 19:23:39 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/august/falls-to-climb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming home today, I over-steered on the slight rise whilst dipping through the short tunnel for the cycle path with the back end of my Scott sliding out from under me in a strange twisting motion. Slid about a metre, with a solid thunk of helmet to concrete before coming to a standstill. There was only superficial damage: a graze to my right hip, and my bike a little out of shape but otherwise functional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing that sucks most is that it&amp;rsquo;s two weeks out before the 90km race for the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.feildingfestivalofcycling.co.nz/&#34;&gt;Feilding Festival of Cycling&lt;/a&gt;. Trying to pull tight, slick lycra shorts over my grace about the size of the bottom of a mug will be rather excruciating if I want to get out on the road to train some more for the race. Instead, the order of the day will be rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s definitely the annoyance of the incident that pisses me off the most. Sure, it&amp;rsquo;s awkward trying to walk after laying down reading an enthralling book or sitting at the computer for a while; but there are emotional pains in my life that cut far, far deeper than physical pain. It&amp;rsquo;s shaping up to be an awfully bad weekend&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mistakes Can Be Wonderful</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/august/mistakes-can-be-wonderful/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 12:58:22 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/august/mistakes-can-be-wonderful/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With the bright, low winter sun streaming through filtered glass into my very warm office, I had attempted to capture more vivid photos of the mini capsicums growing in abundance using a low exposure. Unfortunately, I completely overlooked the factor of which direction the camera was facing, producing extremely dark images than intended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, despite failed manual camera settings, the pictures turned out amazing, as seen in the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#39;imagelink&#39; href=&#39;http://www.flickr.com/photos/jessic4h/4880287773/&#39;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://life.jessicah.org/post/mistakes-can-be-wonderful-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mini Capsicums (1/4)&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#39;imagelink&#39; href=&#39;http://www.flickr.com/photos/jessic4h/4880896722/&#39;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://life.jessicah.org/post/mistakes-can-be-wonderful-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mini Capsicums (2/4)&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here are a couple of other pictures before messing around with the camera settings:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#39;imagelink&#39; href=&#39;http://www.flickr.com/photos/jessic4h/4880246989/&#39;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://life.jessicah.org/post/mistakes-can-be-wonderful-3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mini Capsicums (3/4)&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#39;imagelink&#39; href=&#39;http://www.flickr.com/photos/jessic4h/4880856658/&#39;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://life.jessicah.org/post/mistakes-can-be-wonderful-4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mini Capsicums (4/4)&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I definitely like the under-exposed photos the best though :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strawberries, tomatoes, and perhaps some beans would grow well in this hothouse as well; would make for a beautifully lush and green working environment!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>