<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post/2009/julies on Journal</title>
    <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/july/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post/2009/julies on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 15:54:05 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/july/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Where It At?</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/july/where-it-at/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 15:54:05 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/july/where-it-at/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I ordered my EeeBox yesterday! Comes with a 22&amp;rdquo; display as well. Hopefully the LCD is better than the hopelessly awful similarly sized displays I have here at work. It is a different model though&amp;mdash;we&amp;rsquo;ll see&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, websites and courier companies need better parcel tracking. Website I ordered it from says all items have been supplied. Which simply means courier has picked it up or something. And the courier website has no information on my tracking number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want my EeeBox already! And this whole claim of 1 business day delivery is so rubbish. If that were true, I should have it now! Not tomorrow, or the next day, or next week. I&amp;rsquo;m so impatient.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ugh, Promotion</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/july/ugh-promotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 15:56:38 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/july/ugh-promotion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Soooooo&amp;hellip; turns out Skype had a promotion on at the time I registered and tested calling my phone. Nice of the signup process to &lt;strong&gt;not tell me!&lt;/strong&gt; Well, explains why it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a brighter note, Taras fixed my iNum problem! There a teeny lil setting on my Nokia phone that is set to &lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt; by default. It blocks anonymous callers for Internet calling. And since Google Talk identifies as an anonymous caller, my lil phone replies with &amp;ldquo;488 Not Acceptable Here.&amp;rdquo; So useful&amp;hellip; :P&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yay! My iNum works! I should probably get a real data plan for my phone next.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>