<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post/2009/januaries on Journal</title>
    <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/january/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post/2009/januaries on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 21:37:31 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/january/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting A Lil&#39; Techie</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/january/getting-a-lil-techie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 21:37:31 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/january/getting-a-lil-techie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, I downloaded the public beta of Windows 7, and wow is it different from Vista! At first glance, it seems mostly the same as Vista, but after nosing around one can quickly notice the revamped user interface, which I am totally loving!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And since the Vista installation of my lil&amp;rsquo; EeePC is nagging me to activate&amp;mdash;I used a university copy to &amp;ldquo;test-drive&amp;rdquo; it&amp;mdash;I decided to blow it away and put Windows 7 on it after a brief exploration on a PC I had laying about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After spending hours copying music over to my gorgeous Eee, and getting my N95 working over BlueTooth with it, my Eee has never looked better! Now I get to play, play, play!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The support for iTunes format music and videos in Windows Media Player is absolutely love! I can have my music in my favourite music player without any awful hacks or gaps in playback when there shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, I feel spoiled with Windows 7! Luckily Vista is still a nice OS after using Windows 7, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as bad as having to work with XP after having Vista&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taupo Challenge</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/january/taupo-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2009 16:41:32 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/january/taupo-challenge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;http://cyclechallenge.com&#34;&gt;Great Lake Cycle Challenge&lt;/a&gt; around &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lake_Taupo&#34;&gt;New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s largest lake&lt;/a&gt; was on a day of insane heat and practically no wind. And unfortunately, I had the misfortune of forgetting to apply sun screen to my legs&amp;mdash;the rest of me was fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add to the misery, the GPS in my phone didn&amp;rsquo;t last the distance, so I was only able to record the first 100km of the driest, hottest, longest bike ride I&amp;rsquo;ve done. On the plus side, I managed to come within 15 minutes of my goal to complete the 160km ride in six and a half hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I just need to improve on my hill-climbing so that I can finish in five and a half hours&amp;hellip; but those were some gruelling hills! And coming down-hill was amazing, at a blistering 73km/h, hehe!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>