<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post/2009/septembers on Journal</title>
    <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/september/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post/2009/septembers on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 15:12:00 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/september/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Castelli</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/september/castelli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 15:12:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/september/castelli/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yay! My new Castelli top arrived! I don&amp;rsquo;t know how long it&amp;rsquo;s been sitting in the mail cubicle over at reception, but I have it now! Just a shame that it&amp;rsquo;s raining&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was really worried about the size; ordering online for clothing is difficult enough as it is. But throw in the fact it&amp;rsquo;s cycling clothes, and the difficulties explode. The sizing for cycling clothes generally don&amp;rsquo;t follow normal clothing sizes very well. For example, this top is a medium; I&amp;rsquo;m typically a size small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I rushed to the bathroom to try in on, and it seems to fit well (&lt;strong&gt;breathes sigh of relief&lt;/strong&gt;)! Must get some pictures once the weather improves&amp;hellip; and get my sexy on with this outfit out cycling&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recovery</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/september/recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 19:08:22 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/september/recovery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over four weeks since my cycling accident and fracturing my collarbone. Now I have this not-so-wonderful piece of bone sticking out where it&amp;rsquo;s not supposed to. Other than that, however, I&amp;rsquo;m feeling much better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I decided to put myself to the test, see if I can start riding. I didn&amp;rsquo;t go at all far. I needed to get a few things from my local bike shop, so headed there, decided what to buy, and headed home again. Ride itself was like five minutes each way&amp;mdash;not for at all&amp;ndash;so I decided to sprint a little at each opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered just how incredibly unfit I&amp;rsquo;ve become from four weeks of practically sitting on my bum all day. It sucks. It really, really sucks. The Taupo challenge is just around the corner with less than two months to go. And the Tour de Manawatu a couple weeks before that. My goal this year was for a five and a half hour time for Taupo, but that goal seems a little out of reach now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some serious training will be needed if I hope to get up to where I was before. Preferably, I&amp;rsquo;d like to be further ahead than where I was before&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s a good thing the weather is improving!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>