<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post/2010/januaries on Journal</title>
    <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/january/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post/2010/januaries on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 10:40:24 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/january/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Struggling to Cope</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/january/struggling-to-cope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 10:40:24 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/january/struggling-to-cope/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I got derailed last night, and ended up saying I wanted to go back home. I&amp;rsquo;m such an unstable person. And now I&amp;rsquo;ve ruined everything. Maybe I can make it all alright again&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m sitting in lounge area at a backpackers, writing away on my EeePC, feeling rather miserable about what I have done. We&amp;rsquo;ll see what happens. Not even sure if I can get the overdraft limit I requested for my bank account approved. If not, I&amp;rsquo;ll have to go back home anyway. Have run out of money fairly quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taras is rather annoyed with me too. Since he&amp;rsquo;s been at conference all week, he hasn&amp;rsquo;t really been able to hang out with me either. Hopefully I get to see him after he gets back from his hike tomorrow. Think he&amp;rsquo;s still going for an overnight hike despite the horrible weather outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I dunno how to fix. I actually don&amp;rsquo;t want to go home at all. This is what I get for being so damn emotional and insecure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travels</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/january/travels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 18:35:40 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2010/january/travels/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow begins my holiday. Meeting Ellen, staying in Wanganui with my parents before we head off to Wellington to join up with Taras. They&amp;rsquo;ve been up in Auckland for a week already.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Wellington, and hiking somewhere (if I can get some gear sorted), we&amp;rsquo;ll be heading somewhere into the South Island with our bikes, without much in the way of plans. It&amp;rsquo;s going to be some fairly spontaneous three week crazy holiday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only thing that got me down is being away from my kitten for so long. A month away is a such a long time, especially with her still growing up and being very much in kitten-mode. She&amp;rsquo;s at a good home, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t help with missing her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Miss getting out of the shower to find Boomer sitting on the shower mat waiting for me. Miss having to try fend her off in her attempts to jump onto my shoulder from top of the washing machine whilst drying self after shower. Miss her climbing up my back to perch herself on my shoulder to see what I&amp;rsquo;m doing in the kitchen. And I really miss her snuggles in the morning, and her licking my nose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope she doesn&amp;rsquo;t grow up too much while I&amp;rsquo;m away. I&amp;rsquo;m sure once I start on my holiday, it&amp;rsquo;ll be a little easier&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>