<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post/2009/augusts on Journal</title>
    <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/august/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post/2009/augusts on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 14:04:05 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/august/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash!</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/august/crash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 14:04:05 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/august/crash/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, no dramatic photos! Just the memory of the event, and the pain as a constant reminder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday, I had an inter-club cycling race against the Wanganui Cycling Club. But I didn&amp;rsquo;t last more than 5 minutes into the D grade race. Winding my way down a fast-paced downhill section, I misjudged one of the corners, found myself far too wide of a left-hand turn, and rode off the edge of the road straight into the bank at about 40km/h. I had a tumble or two on the bike along the ditch, landing a couple metres from my bike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Miraculously, it seems my bike came out relatively unscathed. I, however, didn&amp;rsquo;t fare quite as well. I managed to fracture my left collarbone, ending all future cycling for the next 6 to 8 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I&amp;rsquo;m bored out of my mind, waiting to get my appointment for a CT scan and find out if I&amp;rsquo;ll need some surgical intervention or not. Painkillers have me buzzing out a little, and the sling barely helps to keep my shoulder immobile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also given up trying to watch movies&amp;mdash;almost every movie has at least one little scene to give me a fright, making me jump and jarring my shoulder very painfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the end of this week, I think I&amp;rsquo;ll be begging for chores to escape the emptiness of having absolutely nothing to do&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>