<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post/2009/decembers on Journal</title>
    <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/december/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post/2009/decembers on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 18:24:51 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/december/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycled the Lake</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/december/cycled-the-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 18:24:51 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/post/2009/december/cycled-the-lake/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I surprised myself that Saturday in November, after a crazy morning just trying to get organised for the race start for the Lake Taupo Cycle Challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of all things I forgot to bring with me for a cycle race was my bike helmet! I hadn&amp;rsquo;t even realised until I went to go put it on that I realised it wasn&amp;rsquo;t there. So I biked down to the race start, found some helpful helpers that directed me to the Avanti bike shop and bought myself a new helmet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I snuck into a faster start group once I got back after being told it was too late to change my start group, which was a good decision. Half the people in the &amp;ldquo;faster&amp;rdquo; group were too slow anyways, so ended up passing many in the beginning. Note for next year: don&amp;rsquo;t underestimate how well I might do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I passed a few people I recognised, and got quite a few comments about my cycling dress, some thinking it was a netball outfit, grr! And despite a few minutes at a drink stop to refuel, I managed to finish within five minutes of my goal time! I was so impressed with myself to get there in the end. Was feeling nigh on impossible at the seemingly slow speed for the first half of the ride.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next year, I definitely need to aim for a time under five hours, and in the meantime you can find photos of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/jessic4h/sets/72157622958973012/&#34;&gt;me riding around the lake&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>