<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Journal</title>
    <link>https://life.jessicah.org/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 10:34:48 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://life.jessicah.org/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://life.jessicah.org/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 10:34:48 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://life.jessicah.org/page/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about&#34;&gt;About&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tēnā koe, welcome to my corner of the Internet. Tēnā koe, in case you didn&amp;rsquo;t know, is Māori for hello (to one person). You can learn more about greetings and the Māori langage at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tetaurawhiri.govt.nz/learning-maori/tikanga-maori/nga-mihi-greetings/&#34;&gt;Te Taura Whiri i te Reo Māori&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About me: I&amp;rsquo;m a cyclist, web developer, programmer, sysadmin and pianist&amp;mdash;none of which I&amp;rsquo;m exceptional at. I have four gorgeous cats: Mini-Boomer, Orange, Starburst, and Chocolato. And I enjoy living in the smallish &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Zealand&#34;&gt;New Zealand&lt;/a&gt; city of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Palmerston_North&#34;&gt;Te Papaioea/Palmerston North&lt;/a&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s a relatively quiet town surrounded by gorgeous countryside, which makes for wonderful cycling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the day, I can be found in my office at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.massey.ac.nz&#34;&gt;Massey University&lt;/a&gt;. There, I work on my web application, do server admin and other assorted tasks. However, I spend most of my talking and anything that&amp;rsquo;s not work!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, at night, I like to listen to a variety of music and snuggle with my cats. And when the weather isn&amp;rsquo;t too awful, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to fit in as much cycling as possible. I also go to races with the Palmerston North Marist Cycling Club and social rides with the VeloGirls on Tuesdays and the Manawatu Masters Cycling Club on Sundays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;legalese&#34;&gt;Legalese&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Header images courtesy of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flickr.com/photos/13ftfall/&#34;&gt;Ash Asher&lt;/a&gt;. Used by permission. Links to original images available in the footer of each page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>